templatesperfect.com 2010-06-07

# Privacy Policy : Templatesperfect.com

At Templatesperfect.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit Templatesperfect.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.  
**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.  
**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We use third party advertisements on Templatesperfect.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. 

You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy. ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)
